s'up Tamers12345 1 2 3 4 5 feet with
a very special video today so I've been
getting a lot of reviews for this
specific item noise ivy any more quests
for a view of this island sulking around
the collection series now if you're any
true song confam like myself you're
going by the ship I mean each one comes
with like 20 episodes so you get the
full season season to juice and jam time
but of course if you're a Sargon fan
just starting out rock for noobs and
you're gonna be going to getting
volume 1 which comes with the first
button there kicking episodes so yeah so
I guess without viewing with this one
the DVD is really cool
it costs like 20 bucks and some now
you're probably wondering oh my God but
it's not that bad well now effect on the
20 episode so you got have to see you
for 20 bucks clan so for this one
- mmm that's like that's a really good
steal that's like a dollar in episode
which now if you would you take these
into consideration this costs $4.99 for
3 episodes when while they are great
episodes holy that's oh my God
that's like a lot of money
marketing you gonna have to back home
now I you not
holy there is a lot oh there's more
- look at that as you can see
there is a lot I'm not making this booth
all please come with three episodes so
that's oh that's actually pretty
damn good if you think about it so
that's about a dollar and five cents in
episode I buy it so we got they must be
doing something right all right
anyway back to a view only borogroves
all going through stuff developing the
underarms what I pretty good I buy one
thing that is really cool - in this box
comes with the sock alarm greatest hits
which I'll actually I don't know how
they pick them out because they the
eight songs suck balls I guess but it's
not that bad
it says it's a great Athair pull hard
just not if I had to guess it would stop
a tram songs and it's done that to try
to give a small blockage it's so cool
though so I'm not complaining and either
see you now let's let's be real here
should you buy this yeah